Hello everyone, I am Ashish with a new video today.
ICICI Lord announced its fourth quarter
net profit at ₹19, the largest insurance company, with a
final result of ₹19 per share.
Let's learn about
ICICI's fourth quarter
results in detail through this video. If you like this video,
please like and
subscribe to our channel for more such videos.
We do not make any recommendations for
buying or selling stocks. Please do your own
research and
consult your financial advisor before making any investment.
ICICI Lord announced its fourth quarter
results and net premium written stood at ₹
4767 crore, an
increase of 18% year-on-year. ICICI Lord General
Insurance Company Limited on April 17
reported a net profit of ₹519 crore for the year ended March 31, 2024, a growth of 18% year-on-year.
Net premium written increased from ₹447 crore a
year ago to ₹
47767 crore, an increase of 18% year-on-year.  The
company's ratio has
improved and has come down to 2.62% compared to 2.56% year-on-year. In
addition, the company's board has
also recommended a final dividend of ₹ per share. On
April 16, this stock of Insurance Broker was trading at 1654 on BSE,
rising by 1.46 points.
As the market was closed on April 17, we will
get to see its reaction.
After this result on April 18, the share of ICICI Bank
IIC Ltd
reached 1710 on April 18, which
increased by 61 points and is trading at 3.73 points on
April 18. So you
can keep an eye on this stock. Its
result is excellent. So with this, I,
Ashish, conclude today's session.
For more such videos, subscribe to our channel.
We do not make any recommendations for
buying or selling stocks.
Please do your own research and consult
your financial advisor before making any investment.
Thank you.